The Rules of the Game and How to Play:

This game is designed for a maximum of 6 players.
In this version there are 13 rounds and the games ends after the 13th round.

On your turn you start by rolling all 5 dice (Press the Roll button).
After your first roll you can set the dice you want to keep by clicked them.
Similarly, you can choose to roll dice that you have previously "kept" by
clicking on them so they are in the "Rolling Section".
To stop rolling you can press the Done button to score the dice.
However, once you decide to score you cannot change your mind and go back. 
On each turn you get 3 rolls and after the third roll you must score.

There is no rule against rescoring the same spot. Meaning that if you chose to
Score chance on 1 turn, you may rescore that spot on a later turn. 

A list of past winners can be found in the gqame files in the file called winnersList.txt 